<resources>

    <string name="app_name">SafeMindWatch</string>

    <string name="default_web_client_id">808493242507-d1lvdphasrirkb1qnch0gaumg7p4g8bl.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>

    <string name="background_image_desc">Background Image</string>
    <string name="menu_icon_desc">Menu Icon</string>
    <string name="pie_chart_desc">Pie Chart</string>
    <string name="statistics_desc">Statistics</string>
    <string name="abnormal_queries_desc">Abnormal Queries</string>
    <string name="prediction_desc">Mental health Prediction</string>

    <string name="email_verified">Email verified</string>


    //terms and conditions
    <string name="terms_text">
Terms and Conditions:\n
\n
Welcome to Safe Mind Watch. By accessing or using our services, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions along with our Privacy Policy.\n
\n
1. Eligibility and Purpose\n
   I. Safe Mind Watch is intended solely for parents or legal guardians of minors under the age of 17.\n
   II. You must be legally competent to enter into a binding agreement.\n
   III. The app must only be used for monitoring your own child or legal ward.\n
\n
2. Informed Consent\n
   I. You must obtain informed consent from the monitored minor, as required by applicable Indian law.\n
   II. The app must not be used for unauthorized or illegal surveillance of other individuals.\n
\n
3. Data Collection and Usage\n
   I. We collect your child’s search queries, website visits, and online browsing duration to assess digital behavior.\n
   II. AI analysis is used to detect signs of:\n
         • Suicidal ideation\n
         • Depression, anxiety, or emotional distress\n
         • Harmful or inappropriate online content\n
   III. All collected data is end-to-end encrypted during both transmission and storage.\n
\n
4. Data Security and Retention\n
   I. We adhere to the following legal frameworks:\n
        • Information Technology Act, 2000\n
        • IT (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures) Rules, 2011\n
        • Digital Personal Data Protection Act, 2023\n
   II. All data is securely stored on Indian servers or internationally hosted servers compliant with Indian data protection standards.\n
   III. Data is retained for a maximum of 30 days, unless an alert is triggered, in which case it may be retained longer for legal or audit purposes.\n
\n
5. Parental Rights and Controls\n
   I. You have the right to access the data collected from your child’s activity.\n
   II. You may request corrections to inaccurate data or deletion of collected information.\n
   III. You may opt out of any non-essential or marketing-related data processing at any time.\n
\n
6. Alerts and Notifications\n
   I. If our AI system detects signs of severe risk or harm, an SOS alert will be sent to the registered parent or guardian.\n
   II. These alerts are not a substitute for professional medical or psychological consultation.\n
\n
7. Responsible Use\n
   I. You must use Safe Mind Watch ethically and legally.\n
   II. Misuse, including unauthorized surveillance or tampering with the service, is strictly prohibited.\n
   III. We reserve the right to suspend or terminate access in the event of misuse or violation of these Terms.\n
\n
8. Third-Party Sharing\n
   I. We do not sell or share your child’s data with third parties without explicit consent.\n
   II. Exceptions apply only when required by law or government authorities.\n
\n
9. Changes to Terms\n
   I. These Terms may be updated or revised at any time, with or without prior notice.\n
   II. Continued use of the service after changes implies your acceptance of the updated Terms.\n
\n
10. Legal Jurisdiction\n
   I. These Terms are governed by the laws of India.\n
   II. Any disputes shall fall under the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in [Insert Your State, e.g., Tamil Nadu].\n
</string>

    <string name="privacy_text">
Privacy Policy:\n
\n
This Privacy Policy describes how Safe Mind Watch collects, uses, and protects your information. By using our services, you agree to the practices outlined below.\n
\n
1. Data Collection\n
   We collect your child’s search history, websites visited, time spent online, and related activity data to ensure their digital safety.\n
\n
2. Use of AI for Safety Monitoring\n
   Our AI analyzes the collected data to detect early signs of:\n
      • Suicidal thoughts\n
      • Depression\n
      • Harmful behavior\n
      • Unsafe online activity\n
\n
3. Parent Registration Information\n
   We collect the parent or guardian’s email, phone number, and consent details during account setup for verification and alerts.\n
\n
4. Data Storage and Security\n
   All data is encrypted during transmission and securely stored on Indian or legally compliant international servers.\n
\n
5. Data Retention Policy\n
   Data is retained for a maximum of 30 days unless a safety alert is triggered, in which case it may be retained for investigation or audit.\n
\n
6. No Unauthorized Sharing\n
   We do not sell, rent, or share your data with any third party without explicit consent, except where required by law.\n
\n
7. Your Rights\n
   As a parent or guardian, you can:\n
      • Request access to your child’s data\n
      • Ask for corrections\n
      • Request deletion at any time\n
\n
8. Opt-Out Option\n
   You may opt out of non-essential data processing or marketing communications through the app’s settings or by contacting support.\n
\n
9. Compliance with Indian Law\n
   We comply with:\n
     • Information Technology Act, 2000\n
     • Digital Personal Data Protection Act, 2023\n
     • Related Indian child protection laws\n
\n
10. Policy Updates\n
    We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Continued use of the app after changes implies your acceptance of the updated terms.\n
</string>

    <string name="welcome_user">Welcome, User!</string>
    <string name="major_feature">Major Feature</string>
    <string name="footer_text">Developed with ❤ by Virtusolvers</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string-array name="open_status_array">
        <item>All</item>
        <item>Open</item>
        <item>Closed</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rating_array">
        <item>All Ratings</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4 and above</item>
        <item>3 and above</item>
        <item>2 and above</item>
        <item>1 and above</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="settings_icon_desc">Settings</string>







</resources>
